<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<configuration label="Louisville Police Stations">
    <marquee>http://sampleserver1.arcgisonline.com/ArcGIS/rest/services/Louisville/LOJIC_PublicSafety_Louisville/MapServer/3</marquee>
    <items>
<field dated="27/11/2025" description="&lt;b&gt;EOI – NSMA Christmas and New Year Cultural Program 2026 &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Dear NSMA Members,&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;We are inviting Expressions of Interest for cultural performances at our NSMA Christmas and New Year Celebration 2026!&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;If you or your family/group would like to perform, please share the following details:&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;* Participant Name(s)&lt;/br&gt;* Type of Performance (dance, song, skit, instrumental, etc.&lt;/br&gt;* Duration&lt;/br&gt;* Number of Performers&lt;/br&gt;* Any technical requirements (music track, mic, stage setup)&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;For more details or to submit your interest, please contact:&lt;/br&gt;Maya – +64 22 028 1315&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Let’s come together to make this festive season colourful and memorable!&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Thanks&lt;/br&gt;NSMA Committee&lt;/br&gt;"/>	
<field dated="14/11/2025" description="&lt;img src=&quot;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2025/christmas/invite/nsfcShirt.png&quot;/&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;b&gt;NorthShore FC &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;NorthShore FC jersey launch!&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;North Shore FC is proud to announce that our Jersey Sponsors &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;u&gt;Silver sponsor&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Elizabeth Chechi ( Ray White ) &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;u&gt;Gold sponsors&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Indus Mortgages &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt; for their great Support. Thanks to all our Sponsors.&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Thanks&lt;/br&gt;Team NorthShore FC&lt;/br&gt;"/>	
<field dated="05/09/2025" description="&lt;img src=&quot;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2025/onam/2025sponsor.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Dear Members&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Thank you to all our generous sponsors for supporting NSMA Onam Celebration 2025 – Maveli on the Shore. Your contributions make this celebration brighter and more memorable for our community!.&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Thanks&lt;/br&gt;Alex George&lt;/br&gt;"/>
<field dated="21/08/2025" description="&lt;img src=&quot;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2025/onam/2025tugofwar.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Dear Members&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Introducing our tug of war team for Northshore -Mallans Northshore.&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Thanks&lt;/br&gt;Team NSMA&lt;/br&gt;"/>
<field dated="16/08/2025" description="Dear Friends&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Invitation to join Thiruvathira Performance!&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;As part of our upcoming Onam celebration this September, we are organizing a beautiful Thiruvathira dance performance- a cherished tradition celebrating femininity, grace and unity&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;We warmly invite all those interested in participating to come forward&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;if you would like to be a part of this joyful performance, please contact &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;0220281315&lt;/br&gt;0220475500&lt;/br&gt;0226370371&lt;/br&gt;Let’s come together and celebrate the spirit of Onam with rhythm and joy!&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Warm regards&lt;/br&gt;Thomas George&lt;/br&gt;"/>
<field dated="29/07/2025" description="Dear Friends&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;We are excited to announce that NSMA membership for the 2025-26 year is now open!&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;We warmly invite you to be part of another amazing year of community, celebration and connection&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Haven't signed up yet?&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Please complete your membership form here&lt;/br&gt;&lt;a href = 'https://docs.google.com/forms/d/16VyLKYsajkLGCq8fhJwCGTn6guyCDwNyqJmODBSN454/viewform?edit_requested=true'&gt;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/16VyLKYsajkLGCq8fhJwCGTn6guyCDwNyqJmODBSN454/viewform?edit_requested=true&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;This year's membership and annual contribution are vital to help us continue organizing enriching events and supporting our growing NSMA community &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Already signed up but haven't paid the membership fee yet?&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Please make your payment using the details below:-&lt;/br&gt;Bank: BNZ&lt;/br&gt;Account Name: NSMA&lt;/br&gt;Account Number: 02 0278 0295050 05&lt;/br&gt;Reference: Your Name&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Thank you for your continued support and generosity&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Together let's make 2025-26 a vibrant and successful year for NSMA. Let's connect, grow and celebrate as one community&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Warm regards&lt;/br&gt;NSMA Committee&lt;/br&gt;"/>
<field dated="29/06/2025" description="&lt;img src=&quot;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2025/execComm.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Dear Members&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Hearty Congratulations to the NSMA Executive Committee 2025–2026!&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;A new chapter begins!&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Wishing the newly elected team strength, unity, and endless inspiration as you lead our community with passion and purpose.&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Here’s to more vibrant festivals, unforgettable moments, and stronger bonds among the North Shore Malayali family.&lt;/br&gt;Let’s support and celebrate our team as they take NSMA to greater heights!&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Thanks&lt;/br&gt;G.T&lt;/br&gt;"/>
<field dated="19/04/2025" description="&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/reel/DHvJ6QWyKY4/?igsh=MWVjc2t3Z2R3M2h1eg%3D%3D&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2025/arangu/aranguInsta.PNG&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Dear members and friends &lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Fun Video or Arangu 2025&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Thanks&lt;/br&gt;GT"/>
<field dated="28/07/2024" description="&lt;img src=&quot;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2024/NitinPaul.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Dear members and friends &lt;/br&gt; 
&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;/br&gt;As we knows Nithin paul,  the former member of NSMA, has passed away few hour's  before in Australia. Let's pray for the eternal repose his soul and strength for his family.
&lt;/br&gt;
&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Thanks&lt;/br&gt;Shino"/>
<field dated="26/07/2024" description="Hi all&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Northshore Malayali Association invite quotes from photographers for Onam celebration on 30th and 31st August 2024.&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Please contact.  02108241967, 0212127717,0226250905, 0223981038
&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;&lt;/br&gt;Thanks&lt;/br&gt;Team NSMA"/>
<field dated="18-Jun-2024" description="Please Renew Your Valuable Membership with the NORTH SHORE MALAYALI ASSOCIATION!&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;We are excited to announce that we have some fantastic events lined up for the year. To enjoy exclusive member discounts and be a part of our vibrant community, please renew your membership.&lt;br/&gt;Membership Fees:&lt;br/&gt; Family Membership: $20&lt;br/&gt;Individual Membership: $10&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Bank Details:&lt;br/&gt;Bank: BNZ&lt;br/&gt;Account Name: NSMA&lt;br/&gt;Account Number: 02 0278 0295050 05&lt;br/&gt;Reference: NSMA member&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Kind regards&lt;br/&gt;Elizabeth Mohanraj on behalf of Team NSMA"/>
      <field dated="16-Jun-2024" description="We welcome the NSMA Committee 2024-2025 &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;img src='https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2024/2024PanelOut.jpg' /&gt;
" />
<field dated="5-Apr-2024" description="Dear NSMA Members,&lt;br/&gt;Tarasandhya fun invite(fan created)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href='https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QbUjYnBD03k' target='new'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src='https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2024/Tarasandhya/nsmaInvite.PNG' /&gt;&lt;a&gt;" />
<field dated="5-Sep-2023" description="Dear NSMA Members,&lt;br/&gt;Onam greeting&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href='https://fb.watch/mHFEtiQQlL/?mibextid=RUbZ1f' target='new'&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src='https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2023/Onam/fbVideo.PNG' /&gt;&lt;a&gt;" /> 
<field dated="2-Sep-2023" description="HelloEveryone,&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Good evening everyone. NSMA expresses heartfelt gratitude to everyone who has come forward and registered to celebrate Onam 2023 with us on 8th and 9th of September 2023, at Milford school, Auckland. We are proud to have such a dynamic group of people in our community. Registrations have reached more than expected numbers  and we are filling up faster than expected. Hence the committee has come to a unanimous decision of holding off any further registrations, until there is confirmation that we can take in more. So as per this decision the registrations for Onam 2023 will be withdrawn/stopped from 0900 am tomorrow 3/9/23.&lt;br/&gt;Once again we apologize for this abrupt decision made and hope that we have nt disappointed anyone. There will be no more ticket sales from tomorrow. This is a necessary step and is being taken so that the program is carried on smoothly. Those who still wish to participate please make use of this time window and register as soon as possible. Thank you again and Happy Onam.&lt;br/&gt;Kind regards&lt;br/&gt;Team NSMA"/>        
<field dated="27-Aug-2023" description="HelloEveryone,&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Vijin’s family has created a Give a litte  page towards the repatriation cost. Kindly support.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href='https://givealittle.co.nz/cause/with-love-to-vijins-family'&gt;&lt;img src='https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2023/Appeals/vipin.PNG' /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Kind regards&lt;br/&gt;Team NSMA"/>
        <field dated="27-Aug-2023" description="Hello Everyone,&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;urgent prayer and financial support needed for Betsy Alexander who has been diagnosed with malignant sino nasal tumor who requires  urgent chemotherapy and radiation therapy going to india for further treatment..She works as a registered nurse in whangarei hospital only for last 2weeks..Her husband and 10month old baby are in India&lt;br/&gt;Kindly support her and family and remind her in your prayers&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;img src='https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2023/Appeals/BnzBetsy.jpeg' /&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Kind regards&lt;br/&gt;Team NSMA" />        
        <field dated="22-Aug-2023" description="Hello Everyone,&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Invitation to all talented individuals to participate in cultural programs and group performances. If you are keen to be part of this event please register your names.&lt;br/&gt;Contact &lt;br/&gt;Boney Mathew : 0225487385
&lt;br/&gt;Sonia Ritto  : 0223326266&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Kind regards&lt;br/&gt;Team NSMA" />         
      <field dated="10-Aug-2023" description="NSMA presents Mega Thiruvathira &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;img src='https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2023/Onam/OnamThrvthra2023.jpg' /&gt;
" />
        <field dated="22-Aug-2023" description="Get your tickets today‼️‼️
Please click on the link below-.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;a href='https://form.jotform.com/232138142502848'&gt;https://form.jotform.com/232138142502848&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;img src='https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2023/Onam/OnamReg.jpeg' /&gt;
" />        
      <field dated="27-Jul-2023" description="NSMA presents Onam 2023 &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;img src='https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2023/Onam/onam2023Presents.jpg' /&gt;
" />   
      <field dated="26-Jul-2023" description="NSMA executive committe 2023-2024 &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;img src='https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2023/nsmaMembers.jpg' /&gt;
" />         
      <field dated="7-Sep-2022" description="Maestro is in Auckland on 24 Sep 2022 &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;img src='https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2022/Onam/ilayiAuckland.jpeg' /&gt;
" />
      <field dated="10-Sep-2022" description="Indian weekender on next HCI &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;img src='https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2022/Onam/NBhushanHCI.jpeg' /&gt;
" />
      <field dated="30-Mar-2020" description="Please pass this to any Indian national, who needs help due to the lockdown in NZ &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;img src='https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2020/coronoNZIn.jpg' /&gt;
" />
      <field dated="23-Mar-2020" description="Hello Everyone,&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; 
As you will have seen in the media, the Newzealand Prime Minister has announced a range of measures to protect New Zealanders from COVID-19. After midnight Sunday 15 March all people entering NZ from anywhere overseas (with the exception of a small number of Pacific Island nations) will be required to self-isolate for 14 days.This is a significant step undertaken by the Newzealand Government to reduce and slow the transmission of COVID-19 in our community.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
 
If you are planning on going overseas in the near future, strongly encourage you to check the Government’s Safe Travel website ( https://www.safetravel.govt.nz/)which advises New Zealanders to avoid all non-essential travel overseas. If you must still travel, the government will require you to self-isolate for 14 days upon returning to NZ.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; 
Kind regards&lt;br/&gt;
Team NSMA
" />
<field dated="5-Sep-2019" description="&lt;img src='https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2019/kiran2019.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Dear friends,&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;With profound sorrow, NSMA announces the sad demise of Mr. Kiran George Jose, in a fatal car accident in Waikato this evening.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Kiran is the Brother-in-Law of Mrs. Shona Anil and Dona Xaviour and the co-brother of Mr. Anil and Xavier, who are the active members of Northshore Malayali Association.The President and executive committee of Northshore Malayali association express our heartfelt condolences to the bereaved family. Kindly join all our prayers for eternal peace to the departed soul.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Thanking you&lt;br/&gt;TEAM NSMA
"/>
<field dated="30-Jan-2018" description="With immense sorrow, we inform you the sad demise of Mrs Teena Kunjappan (29), a native of  Kundara, Kollam. Teena is the tragic victim of an accidental drowning at Tahunanui Beach, Nelson, 
where she and her husband Mr. Jilu C John had gone for a stroll. She died at the scene before the arrival of the emergency services and Jilu was taken to Nelson Hospital in a moderate condition.
We are looking forward for helping the family for the repatriation to India. Kindly, come forward for raising funds to help the family, 
Please use below link for ur contributions.&lt;br&gt; &lt;xlink:href='https://givealittle.co.nz/cause/raising-money-to-repatriate-the-remains-of-mrs' 
xlink:show='new'/&gt;
"/>
      <field dated="07-Jan- 2018" description="It is with sorror we inform you the sad demise of Mr V.V Cherian (87), Valiyaveetil, father of Siby cherian residing at 2/23 Brooke street Milford. He passed away in kerala and the funeral will be held on 8th -Jan-2018 at 10 am at kudamaloor church. Please put together all our prayers for the departed soul.&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;img src='https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2018/Notices/Siby.jpg' /&gt;
"/>
    </items>
</configuration>

