<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<configuration label="Louisville Police Stations">
    <marquee>http://sampleserver1.arcgisonline.com/ArcGIS/rest/services/Louisville/LOJIC_PublicSafety_Louisville/MapServer/3</marquee>
    <items>
      <field dated="23-Nov-2018" description="Dear Members,&lt;br/&gt;Northshore malayali association will be celebrating our Christmas and New year programme on 5th of January 2019 at Takapuna War Memorial Hall. The programme will commence at 5pm. We are planning to hold a night with entertainment and fun. We request your complete co-operation to make this a success. Lets all celebrate this Xmas and New year with a joyful spirit.&lt;br/&gt;
We are expecting enrollments for different entertainment items, so interested individuals please come forward and contact us. We have arranged a committee for the above and the contact numbers are mentioned below.&lt;br/&gt;
Venue: Glenfield college theatre, 60 Kaipatiki Rd, Glenfield&lt;br/&gt;
Once again reminding you the date of the function will be 5th January 2019, and the venue - Takapuna War Memorial Hall and the time - 5 pm.
MERRY CHRISTMAS & HAPPY NEW YEAR. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
.&lt;br/&gt;
സ്നേഹത്തോടെ,  &lt;br/&gt;
നോർത്ത് ഷോർ മലയാളി അസോസിയേഷൻ" />
      <field dated="15-Apr-2018" description="Dear NSMA Members,&lt;br/&gt;We cordially invite all of you and your families to the NSMA Arangu- Music and Dance Festival- 2018.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
When: Saturday, the 21st Apr 2018&lt;br/&gt;
Venue: Glenfield college theatre, 60 Kaipatiki Rd, Glenfield&lt;br/&gt;
Let’s all celebrate together and make this event a grant success. &lt;br/&gt;
.&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;img src='https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2018/Arangu/Arangu2018.jpg' /&gt;
സ്നേഹത്തോടെ,  &lt;br/&gt;
നോർത്ത് ഷോർ മലയാളി അസോസിയേഷൻ" />
<field dated="30-Jan-2018" description="With immense sorrow, we inform you the sad demise of Mrs Teena Kunjappan (29), a native of  Kundara, Kollam. Teena is the tragic victim of an accidental drowning at Tahunanui Beach, Nelson, 
where she and her husband Mr. Jilu C John had gone for a stroll. She died at the scene before the arrival of the emergency services and Jilu was taken to Nelson Hospital in a moderate condition.
We are looking forward for helping the family for the repatriation to India. Kindly, come forward for raising funds to help the family, 
Please use below link for ur contributions.&lt;br&gt; &lt;xlink:href='https://givealittle.co.nz/cause/raising-money-to-repatriate-the-remains-of-mrs' 
xlink:show='new'/&gt;
"/>
      <field dated="07-Jan- 2018" description="It is with sorror we inform you the sad demise of Mr V.V Cherian (87), Valiyaveetil, father of Siby cherian residing at 2/23 Brooke street Milford. He passed away in kerala and the funeral will be held on 8th -Jan-2018 at 10 am at kudamaloor church. Please put together all our prayers for the departed soul.&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;img src='https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2018/Notices/Siby.jpg' /&gt;
"/>
      <field dated="30-Dec-2017" description="Dear NSMA Members,&lt;br/&gt;We cordially invite all of you and your families to the NSMA Christmas and New Year celebrations 2018.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
When: Saturday, the 13th January 2018&lt;br/&gt;
Venue: The Forrest Hill Primary School&lt;br/&gt;
Time: 6pm onwards&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
Kindly bring $1 coins to participate in variety of exciting games arranged just for you. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
Entry requirements: &lt;br/&gt;
Adults: $20 &lt;br/&gt;
Kids: $10 (age 5-15) &lt;br/&gt;
Guests: $25 &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
Last date to buy your coupons will be on 10/01/2018. &lt;br/&gt;
Let’s all celebrate together and make this event a grant success. &lt;br/&gt;
For coupons, please contact : &lt;br/&gt;
Binu - 0223210823 &lt;br/&gt;
Siby - 0211440581 &lt;br/&gt;
Martin - 0272748931 &lt;br/&gt;
Jose - 0220997757 &lt;br/&gt;
Unni - 0211296136 &lt;br/&gt;
Deepa - 0212127717 &lt;br/&gt;
Shino - 02108241967 &lt;br/&gt;
Vishal - 02102248998 &lt;br/&gt;
Deepu - 0223440305 &lt;br/&gt;
സ്നേഹത്തോടെ,  &lt;br/&gt;
നോർത്ത് ഷോർ മലയാളി അസോസിയേഷൻ" /> 
    </items>
</configuration>

