<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<configuration label="Louisville Police Stations">
    <marquee>http://sampleserver1.agol.com/LOJIC_PublicSafety_Louisville/MapServer/3</marquee>
    <items>
      <field dated="9-Sep-2022" description="Dear Brothers and sisters,&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; 
we are getting  close to our onam celebration. We would like to do a head count for the day for the purpose of booking sadhya. Those who are  interested please PM your details and the number of people coming to the function. 
My number is 0221605634 #Tony. :&lt;br/&gt;
Once again the per head charges for the function is:&lt;br/&gt;
Adults : 30$head:&lt;br/&gt;
Kids 5-12yrs: 15$head:&lt;br/&gt;
Below 5yrs: free.:&lt;br/&gt;
Payments can be made online or on the day at the function. Please make sure to flick me a message. :&lt;br/&gt;
Happy onam. :&lt;br/&gt;
Thanks:&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;img src='https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2022/Onam/Events.jpeg' /&gt;

Team NSMA


" />
      <field dated="10-Sep-2022" description="Dear Brothers and sisters,&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; 
Please find our sponsors for Onam:&lt;br/&gt;

&lt;img src='https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2022/Onam/Sponsors.jpeg' /&gt;

Team NSMA


" />
      <field dated="10-Sep-2022" description="Dear Brothers and sisters,&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; 
Please find the promotional intro video for Onam:&lt;br/&gt;


&lt;video width='320' height='240' controls/&gt;
  &lt;source src='https://youtu.be/s7O710p21yk' type='video/mp4'/&gt;
Your browser does not support the video tag.
&lt;/video&gt;


Team NSMA


" />
      <field dated="12-Jan-2021" description="Dear Brothers and sisters,&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; 
The day has arrived. We are just few  hours away from the much awaited Christmas New year  Celebration 2021, It is the merriest time of the year, getting together with friends and families to celebrate the time with Dance , Good  food, live music and grace. we hope you all join us with your family on Saturday 13th February 2021 4.30pm to 10pm@ St Joseph school auditorium. the program start with funny games followed by cultural programs. There are few changes for our program due to unexpected circumstances our Tug of  war competition has been canceled. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;

 
Once again reminding you the date for the event will be:&lt;br/&gt;
Date: 13th February Saturday 2021.&lt;br/&gt;
Venue :  St.Joseph School auditorium @ 4.30. pm onwards.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; 

We kindly request you all to pay the entry fee  in advance by account through or pay at the counter by cash or Eftpos.&lt;br/&gt;
NSMA Account # - 02 02778 0295050 05&lt;br/&gt;
Adults and Guest - $25&lt;br/&gt;
KIds (5 to 12)   - $15&lt;br/&gt;
Kids under  age 5 free&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;

Any inquiries please contact - &lt;br/&gt;
Thomas Padassery (president)@ 0211858252&lt;br/&gt;
Tony Skariah( secretary)@ 0221605634 &lt;br/&gt;
Derik Xavier( Treasurer)@  0210233144 &lt;br/&gt;  

&lt;img src='https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2021/Christmas2021.jpeg' /&gt;

 

&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; 
Kind regards&lt;br/&gt;
Team NSMA
" />
      <field dated="5-Sep-2019" description="Dear Brothers and sisters,&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; 
As we are all still on a stage of bereavement with loss of our beloved Kiran,
The Executive committee of Northshore Malayali Association has decided to Postpone
Our Onam celebration to a later date.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
 
We will be conducting our Onam 2019 celebrations on 28th  of September 2019 Saturday. 
 
Sorry for the inconvenience this has created.
 
We recognise that the support to the family of Kiran is more relevant at this stage.
 
We will update the further details about our Onam celebrations on our upcoming emails.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt; 
Kind regards&lt;br/&gt;
Team NSMA
" />
      <field dated="15-Aug-2019" description="&lt;img src='https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2019/Onam2019.jpg' /&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;DEAR BROTHERS AND SISTERS,&lt;br/&gt;
Yesss... we are all waiting for that DAY ...its our ONAM. How exciting..&lt;br/&gt;
Let our Onam be filled with Joy, Peace, Prosperity and Happiness.
Our Northshore Malayali Association welcome you all to the festival, an amazing Onam Celebration here in Northshore.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
The ONAM 2019 Celebrations will be held at Milford primary school.The dates will be on 06/09/2019 and 07/09/2019. SAVE THE DATES PLEASE.&lt;br/&gt;
NSMA organizing northern region TUG OF WAR competition On the 7th September 2019 after our ONASADHYA.It will be a fun time for all of us to celebrate it together.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
Once again we welcome you all in to the great event.&lt;br/&gt;
Onam tickets.&lt;br/&gt;
Members 25$&lt;br/&gt;
Guest       30$&lt;br/&gt;
Kids above 5years old 15$.&lt;br/&gt;
Vadam vali registration 150$&lt;br/&gt;
7 person 600kg per team. &lt;br/&gt;
Also we have QUIZ competition for KIDS under 15year old, TOPIC is KERALA and ONAM must be a 2 people group. Parents please prepare the kids for the competition.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Onam 2019 Programme list&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
Day 1 (06/09/2019)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
*Quiz competition for kids ( 5 to 15 years of age) – Topic “ Keralam and Onam&lt;br/&gt;
*Caroms for men and women.&lt;br/&gt;
*Arm Wrestling for Men and women.&lt;br/&gt;
*Note picking for kids and ladies.&lt;br/&gt;
*Musical Chair Ladies, gents and kids.&lt;br/&gt;
*Candle lighting men and women (15 years and above).&lt;br/&gt;
*Coin in the bucket for kids ( 5 to 15 years of age)&lt;br/&gt;
*Sundarikk Pottuthodal adults 15 and above&lt;br/&gt;
*Spinning goal adults men and women (15 years and above).&lt;br/&gt;
*Memory check – Kids ( 5 to 15 Years)&lt;br/&gt;
*Vadam vali Kids and women.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Day 2 (07/09/2019)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
09.00 am start&lt;br/&gt;
Kids Games  ( Frog Jumping, Candy picking, Speech- Topic AMMA (Mother)&lt;br/&gt;
10.00 am&lt;br/&gt;
Inauguration&lt;br/&gt;
Thuruvathira by Northshore ladies and kids.&lt;br/&gt;
10.45 am&lt;br/&gt;
Couple run&lt;br/&gt;
‘Biscuit kadi Men and women ( above 15 years)&lt;br/&gt;
Kalam thallippottikkal – Adults ( men and women)&lt;br/&gt;
11.30 am&lt;br/&gt;
Onasadhya&lt;br/&gt;
01.30 pm&lt;br/&gt;
Northern region “Tug of War” competition&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
May the spirit of Onam guide you in your life, Let it live inside your heart. Fulfil what you desire and hope for the best.&lt;br/&gt;
Thanking you&lt;br/&gt;
The NSMA team
" />
      <field dated="15-Apr-2019" description="Dear NSMA Members,&lt;br/&gt;We cordially invite all of you and your families to the NSMA Arangu- Music and Dance Festival- 2019.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
When: Saturday, the 4th May 2019&lt;br/&gt;
Venue: Glenfield college theatre, 60 Kaipatiki Rd, Glenfield&lt;br/&gt;
Let’s all celebrate together and make this event a grant success. &lt;br/&gt;
.&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;img src='https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2019/Arangu.jpg' /&gt;
സ്നേഹത്തോടെ,  &lt;br/&gt;
നോർത്ത് ഷോർ മലയാളി അസോസിയേഷൻ" />
      <field dated="15-Apr-2018" description="The St Alphonsa group is carrying out thier carols on 12th and 15th Dec. The schedule is as below &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;img src='https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2018/Notices/2018-christmasNotice-2.jpg' /&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;img src='https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2018/Notices/2018-christmasNotice-1.jpg' /&gt;
" />
      <field dated="23-Nov-2018" description="Dear Members,&lt;br/&gt;Northshore malayali association will be celebrating our Christmas and New year programme on 5th of January 2019 at Takapuna War Memorial Hall. The programme will commence at 5pm. We are planning to hold a night with entertainment and fun. We request your complete co-operation to make this a success. Lets all celebrate this Xmas and New year with a joyful spirit.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
We are expecting enrollments for different entertainment items, so interested individuals please come forward and contact us. We have arranged a committee for the above and the contact numbers are mentioned below.&lt;br/&gt;
Dayana Nivil - 0211509159 &lt;br/&gt;
Pallavi Unni - 02102636598 &lt;br/&gt;
Tintu Basil - 0223764371 &lt;br/&gt;
Shino Thomas - 02108241967 &lt;br/&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;
Once again reminding you the date of the function will be 5th January 2019 and the venue - Takapuna War Memorial Hall and the time - 5 pm.
MERRY CHRISTMAS and a HAPPY NEW YEAR
.&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
സ്നേഹത്തോടെ,  &lt;br/&gt;
നോർത്ത് ഷോർ മലയാളി അസോസിയേഷൻ" />
      <field dated="15-Apr-2018" description="Dear NSMA Members,&lt;br/&gt;We cordially invite all of you and your families to the NSMA Arangu- Music and Dance Festival- 2018.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
When: Saturday, the 21st Apr 2018&lt;br/&gt;
Venue: Glenfield college theatre, 60 Kaipatiki Rd, Glenfield&lt;br/&gt;
Let’s all celebrate together and make this event a grant success. &lt;br/&gt;
.&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;img src='https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2018/Arangu/Arangu2018.jpg' /&gt;
സ്നേഹത്തോടെ,  &lt;br/&gt;
നോർത്ത് ഷോർ മലയാളി അസോസിയേഷൻ" />
<field dated="30-Jan-2018" description="With immense sorrow, we inform you the sad demise of Mrs Teena Kunjappan (29), a native of  Kundara, Kollam. Teena is the tragic victim of an accidental drowning at Tahunanui Beach, Nelson, 
where she and her husband Mr. Jilu C John had gone for a stroll. She died at the scene before the arrival of the emergency services and Jilu was taken to Nelson Hospital in a moderate condition.
We are looking forward for helping the family for the repatriation to India. Kindly, come forward for raising funds to help the family, 
Please use below link for ur contributions.&lt;br&gt; &lt;xlink:href='https://givealittle.co.nz/cause/raising-money-to-repatriate-the-remains-of-mrs' 
xlink:show='new'/&gt;
"/>
      <field dated="07-Jan- 2018" description="It is with sorror we inform you the sad demise of Mr V.V Cherian (87), Valiyaveetil, father of Siby cherian residing at 2/23 Brooke street Milford. He passed away in kerala and the funeral will be held on 8th -Jan-2018 at 10 am at kudamaloor church. Please put together all our prayers for the departed soul.&lt;br/&gt;
&lt;img src='https://raw.githubusercontent.com/joseph-jose/www/master/2018/Notices/Siby.jpg' /&gt;
"/>
      <field dated="30-Dec-2017" description="Dear NSMA Members,&lt;br/&gt;We cordially invite all of you and your families to the NSMA Christmas and New Year celebrations 2018.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
When: Saturday, the 13th January 2018&lt;br/&gt;
Venue: The Forrest Hill Primary School&lt;br/&gt;
Time: 6pm onwards&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
Kindly bring $1 coins to participate in variety of exciting games arranged just for you. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
Entry requirements: &lt;br/&gt;
Adults: $20 &lt;br/&gt;
Kids: $10 (age 5-15) &lt;br/&gt;
Guests: $25 &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
Last date to buy your coupons will be on 10/01/2018. &lt;br/&gt;
Let’s all celebrate together and make this event a grant success. &lt;br/&gt;
For coupons, please contact : &lt;br/&gt;
Binu - 0223210823 &lt;br/&gt;
Siby - 0211440581 &lt;br/&gt;
Martin - 0272748931 &lt;br/&gt;
Jose - 0220997757 &lt;br/&gt;
Unni - 0211296136 &lt;br/&gt;
Deepa - 0212127717 &lt;br/&gt;
Shino - 02108241967 &lt;br/&gt;
Vishal - 02102248998 &lt;br/&gt;
Deepu - 0223440305 &lt;br/&gt;
സ്നേഹത്തോടെ,  &lt;br/&gt;
നോർത്ത് ഷോർ മലയാളി അസോസിയേഷൻ" /> 
    </items>
</configuration>